The only easy day was yesterday.
Act of Valor is a action, thriller, war film directed by Mike McCoy.
When a covert mission to rescue a kidnapped CIA operative
uncovers a chilling plot, an elite, highly trained U.S.
SEAL team speeds to hotspots around the globe, racing against
the clock to stop a deadly terrorist attack.
Lisa Morales, played by Roselyn Sánchez.
Abu Shabal, played by Jason Cottle.
Christo, played by Alex Veadov.
Walter Ross, played by Nestor Serrano.
LT Rorke's Wife, played by Ailsa Marshall.
Commander Pedros, played by Gonzalo Menendez.
Act of Valor is a 2012 American action film produced and directed by
Mouse McCoy and Scott Waugh and written by Kurt Johnstad.
The film stars active duty U.S.
Navy SEALs and U.S.
Navy Special Warfare Combatant-craft Crewmen, as well as Roselyn Sánchez,
Jason Cottle, Alex Veadov, Nestor Serrano, and Emilio Rivera.
Act of Valor was released in the United States on
February 24, 2012, by Relativity Media.
The film received generally negative reviews from critics, but was a box office success,
grossing over $81 million worldwide against a production budget of $12 million.
It was nominated for Best Original Song at the 70th Golden Globe Awards.
The film explores themes of navy, submarine,
heroism, scuba diving, u.s. navy seal.
The tone is intense.